travelerseek.com 2017-11-13

# TravelerSeek | Privacy

Privacy

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

U.S. lawmakers draw up new North Korea sanctions   
Mae Owen - Nov 03, 2017   
Republican and Democratic U.S. Senators agreed to a new package of sanctions Wednesday that targets financial institutions that do business with North Korea. 

U.S. pursues direct talks with North Korea, despite Trump   
Tyler Henderson - Nov 02, 2017   
The talks aim to rein in North Korea's weapons programs, secure the release of U.S. prisoners held in North Korea, and more generally improve bilateral relations, Time will tell if they make progress on any of these objectives, however. 

Climate change is harming human health   
Harry Marcolis - Nov 02, 2017   
A new report shows that climate change is triggering deadly events that are harming millions of people across the globe.

Filipino strongman Duterte says Trump needs to "tone down" North Korea talk   
Joyce Clark - Nov 02, 2017   
Philippine President Rodrigo Duterte is not known for mincing words, but he said that President Trump needs to stop threatening North Korea. Duterte will talk North Korea strategy with Trump and other regional leaders in the coming month.

Chinese test "death zone" spy drones that are nearly invisible to radar   
Vicky Webb - Nov 02, 2017   
China is testing new bat-sized spy drones that cost less than $200 per drone, are almost invisible to radar, and fly as high as 12 miles above sea level. This altitude puts them in near space, high enough to evade the anti-aircraft fire that can shoot down other drones.
